Finding Aid for the Donald Kalish Papers LSC.0578
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Various items, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Invasion of Lebanon leaflets, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Lebanon invasion magazine and newspaper clippings, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Concerned Faculty steering committee meeting, 1982 February 24 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Bills and receipts for November 11, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Concerned Faculty activity, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Program to be sent to faculty, 1981 November 11 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Letter to entire faculty, 1981 November (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Draft of letter to entire faculty, 1981 November (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Letters of invitation to November 11th (Fall), 1981 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Financial data: May 1981 event and Bruin advert (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Concerned Faculty efforts and clippings (Spring), 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Hunter College teach-in, 1981 November 5 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Contributions, data on them, undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Letter to medical school for funds, 1981 November 12 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- "Movers and Shakers" and correspondence, 1981 November 9 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Agenda and finance report, 1981 November 18 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Kunzl, El Salvador film, and freeze, 1981 November (Box 67, Folder 7)
- El Salvador and New Cold War clippings (Spring), 1981 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- For Hobson meeting, 1981 September 16 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- UC mailing service contacts and printing costs, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Karl-Heinz Hansen material (Fall), 1981 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Correspondence on November 11 non-responses, 1981 December (Box 67, Folder 12)
- List of those identified with Concerned Faculty, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Concerned Faculty membership and contact info, undated (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Telephone receipts, 1981-1983 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Films, 1981 November (Box 67, Folder 16)
- UCS materials prior to November 11 event (Fall), 1981 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- UCS documentation material, 1981 November 11 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- UCS newsletter (Fall), 1981 (Box 67, Folder 19)
- UCS material (Summer-Fall), 1981 (Box 67, Folder 20)
- Notes on 7/19/81 and 11/11/81 events (Box 67, Folder 21)
- Concerned Faculty's four lunches at Joyce's, 1983 May (Box 67, Folder 22)
- Concerned Faculty: Early data, agenda, and minutes for November 11 (Fall), 1981 (Box 67, Folder 23)
- "Sheepskin: Anton and Thalheimer Strike at SF State: The Story", 1970 March 2 (Box 67, Folder 24)
- San Francisco State advert, 1968-1969 (Box 67, Folder 25)
- Ziferstein, Isidore, 1965-1967 (Box 67, Folder 26)
- Prisoner information, 1965-1970 (Box 67, Folder 27)
- Newspaper articles, 1967 November 28 (Box 67, Folder 28)
- Articles filed for Philosophy 150B, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 29)
- Anti-war articles and photographs, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 30)
- Articles: Kunstler interview in Playboy, "Criminal Trials of Repression," and Sam Brown, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Biographies: Goldberger, Keeny, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Goldberger photograph, 1981 October (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Program, 1981 November 11 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Attendance lists and sign-ups for service (Fall), 1981 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- October 7 handout, statement of purpose and program, 1981 October 1 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Revision of program for steering committee, 1981 October 10 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Previous Concerned Faculty meetings (Fall), 1981 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Concerned Faculty letter of invitation to October 7, 1981 September (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Daily Bruin article on October 7 event, 1981 October 9 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Henry Steele Commager magazine articles, 1967-1970 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Tenure controversy, Kurzweil case, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Academic freedom, S. Lynd (Fall), 1967 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- UC Regulations on Use of Resources and academic freedom, 1970 September 28 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Articles on role of the university by Dowd, Trow, and Etzioni, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Education and the barricades, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 32: Exams (Holly Thomas, Bernie Kobes, Keith Simmons, Anderson), 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Course evaluations Philosophy 31 and 32, and salary increase, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures (Spring), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Promoting KM2 and errors, 1979-1981 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Judy letter and errata list, 1982 March 2 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- Incidental set theory, and C.C. Chang final, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 22)
- Some proofs by Holly Thomas (Spring), 1978 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Natural numbers, Enderton, undated (Box 68, Folder 24)
- Philosophy M221A: Set theory and lectures (Spring), 1976 (Box 68, Folder 25)
- A x A A for not finite A equivalent to axiom of choice (Spring), 1975 (Box 68, Folder 26)
- Philosophy 134: Records (Winter), 1974 (Box 68, Folder 27)
- Philosophy 32: Exams, 1970-1979 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 32: Final exams (Winter), 1987 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 32: Final exams (Winter), 1988 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- "Current progress on 'at least six' ", 1988 December (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 32: Records (Winter), 1984 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 32 and 133 materials (Winter), 1987 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 32: Final and answers (Winter), 1988 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 32: Final exam (Winter), 1988 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 32: Expansions, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 32: Exercise I, UI/EG, and answers (Winter), 1988 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 32: Proof of T263 by cases (Winter), 1988 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 32: Exercise 34, honors group, and "Fool the People" (Winter), 1988 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 32: First homework assignment (Winter), 1988 January (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 32: Midterm and answers (Winter), 1988 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 32: Records and course evaluations (Winter), 1985 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 32: Records and copy of final (Winter), 1989 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures notes (Winter), 1989 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures, proofs, syllabus, and Mar's problem (Winter), 1976 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures, exercises and solutions (Winter), 1989 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures, exams and incidentals (Winter), 1985 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures, exams, and problems (Winter), 1984 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures, syllabus, and records (Winter), 1977 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Cleaver issue clippings, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Senate meeting, Cleaver issue correspondence and bulletins, 1968 September 30 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Student education policy commissioner and teaching resources, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Riots newspaper articles, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Faculty meeting on "Stop the Draft Week" and articles, 1967 October 7 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Clippings, 1967 September (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Implementation of Academic Senate by-law 188, news clippings, 1967 September-October (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Newspaper articles, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Newspaper articles, 1969 November-December (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Newspaper articles, 1969 September-October (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Various newspaper articles, 1969 August (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Articles on anti-war issues, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- RAP Brown trial newspaper clippings, 1970 March (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Articles on Angela Davis, 1970 February-March, 1969 September-October (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Student Democratic Society newspaper clippings, 1969 June (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Articles on Muhammed Ali's trial, 1969 July (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Clippings on Dr. Benjamin Spock draft conspiracy conviction, undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Articles on Robert Williams, 1969 September (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Articles and correspondence on Black Student Unions and resistance, 1968-1971 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Articles on various political topics, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- News outline and bulletins, 1969 May- December (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Newspaper clippings on Vietnam, 1967 July- October (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings on student power and tuition (Winter), 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Kaufman's moratorium speech, 1969 November 15 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Articles, essays, and pamphlets on Nixon and Humphrey, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Newspaper article on Reagan budget cuts, 1970 February 22 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Clippings on Vietnam, Martin Luther King, and Benjamin Spock, 1968 April 19-20 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Clippings on UC budget and political involvement, 1968 March 24 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- News article on racial discrimination at San Jose State, 1967 September 24 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Clippings on Vietnam, 1967 September (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Clippings on Latin America and Bolivia on Che Guevara, 1967 September 23 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Clippings on UCLA and UC San Diego, 1967 September 23-24 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Clippings on Vietnam, 1967 July 29 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Clippings, 1967 September (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Clippings on Vietnam, 1967 September-December (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Clippings, 1967 August, October-November (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Vietnam Education Project newsletters, 1968 June- December, 1969 January-February (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Tri-Continental Information Center bulletins, 1967 May - 1968 May (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Articles on UCLA minorities and Student Democratic Society, 1969 August 22 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Some articles on Chomsky, undated (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Rich Morrow school schedule, 1972-1974 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- Clippings, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- Some references, notes, clippings, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Political movement materials, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Brugger sit-in and sentencing for misdemeanor cases (Spring), 1970 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Clippings on Vietnam, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Clippings on Communism and Vietnam, March 1968 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Clippings on McCarthy, 1967-1968 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Case materials (Summer), 1969 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Greg Sheridan correspondence and paper (Fall), 1973 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Elain Thro, proposition paper and correspondence, undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Cathy Harlow's proposition, undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Paper by Harry Deutsch, undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Palle Yourgrau doctoral paper, 1977 July 5, 1978 May 16 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Donald Brown paper, 1978 March (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Malitz, "NPI", 1974 March 12 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Notes and info on Malitz paper, 1973 December - 1974 June (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Malitz's dissertation chapters 1-2, undated (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Malitz's dissertation, undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Additional pages to Malitz dissertation, undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Clippings on Black Power movement, 1969 December, 1970 February-March (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Clippings on political action on campus, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Clippings on political activity on UC campus, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Papers and pamphlets related to anti-Vietnam War march, 1969 November (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Clippings on various political issues (Spring), 1968 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Clippings on Vietnam, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Transcripts conspiracy and contempt charges, 1970 February 14-15 (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
- Chicago Conspiracy Trial transcript, 1970 January 8 (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
- Peoples' Assembly Chicago Democratic Convention clippings and correspondence, 1968 August 24-29 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Peoples' Assembly Chicago Democratic Convention legal defense materials, 1970 February-April, September (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Peoples' Assembly Chicago Democratic Convention materials on Vietnam, 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- News articles and outlines, 1970-1971 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Vietnam War related material, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 5-6)
- Conspiracy trial news articles, 1970 February, November (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Conspiracy trial news articles, 1970 January (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Conspiracy trial news articles, 1969 December (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Conspiracy trial news articles, 1969 November (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Conspiracy trial news articles, 1969 March- October (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Newspaper clippings on Ellsburg/Russo, Grand Jury secrecy, and draft counseling, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 6-7)
- Correspondence and newspaper clippings, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Correspondence and newspaper clippings, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Mail and pamphlets, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- News clippings, 1969 March-April (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Package from LA Peace Directory, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Concerned Faculty: Correspondence, newspaper clippings, and articles, 1991-1993 (Box 79, Folder 6-10)
- Philosophy 184: Exams and initial bibliography, undated (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 184: Mimeograph Polish notation (Spring), 1954 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 184: Sentential logic and a metatheorem manuscript (Spring), 1954 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 184: Manuscript and notes on sentential calculus (Spring), 1954 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 184: Axiom yield results (Spring), 1954 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 184: Lectures on sentential calculus (Spring), 1954 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 184: Normal form, alternative axiom sets, and deduction theorem (Spring), 1952-1954 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 184: Sentential calculus, deductive completeness and disjunction (Spring), 1954 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 184: Quin's method of logic (Spring), 1952 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 184: Predicate calculus (Spring), 1955 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 184: Syllabus on sentential calculus (Spring), 1954 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 125: Syllabus and gradebook (Spring, Winter), 1968 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 125: Exams 30, 102, and 125 (Winter), 1968 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 102: Bibliography and syllabus, undated (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 125: Syllabus, undated (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 102: Valid syllogisms, arithmetic theorems, and Sancho Panza problem, undated (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 30: Inductive logic notes and syllabus (Spring), 1954 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 30: "Thought Problems," material fallacies, and Humes argument (Spring), 1955 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 30: Induction and probability bibliography, undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 30: Syllabus (Fall), 1956 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Peano's arithmetic, extended, undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Notes on Carnap's probability, undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 30 (Spring), 1959 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Recursive functions notes from Robinson, undated (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Nino's syllabus for sentential logic, undated (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 30: Montague's syllabus (Spring), 1960 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 102: Exams and notes (Fall), 1962 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 30 and 10 notes on sentential logic, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 102: Outline, homework, and exams (Spring), 1965 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 102: Robinson's final (Fall), 1963 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 30: Exposition of Mill's methods outline (Fall), 1954 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Philosophy 370: Records and exams (Spring), 1961 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- Philosophy 102: Peano's arithmetic extended, undated (Box 81, Folder 19)
- Engineering 105A: Morgan, notes, syllabus, sets, functions, and problems (Spring), 1961 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Notes on Reichenbach's nomological statements (Summer), 1952 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 185: H. Reichenbach lecture notes (Spring), 1950 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- "An Axiomatization of the Cumulative Theory of Types" by Dana Scott at Stanford (Fall), 1963 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- "Paradox of Confirmation," G. von Wright, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Robinson 191: Rough notes, induction problems, and recursivity (Fall), 1962 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Kalish-Montague: Kleene hierarchy (Fall), 1962 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Philosophy Club, phenomenological research, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Sobel on translations, undated (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Notes by Howard Sobel and Philosophy 6b-2 (Baye's Rule, conceivability), undated (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Pragmatics and set theory, Richard Montague, undated (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Buridan's Sophisma, undated (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Poor notes from lectures by church, undated (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Notes on Reichenbach and theory of probability (Spring), 1952 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Deduction of old version notes and bibliography, undated (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Remarks on first-order logic, Montague-Kalish, undated (Box 82, Folder 16)
- Remarks on first-order logic, Montague-Kalish, undated (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Descriptions and natural deduction, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Description and natural deduction, older version, undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Some remarks on first-order logic, Montague-Kalish (Winter), 1956 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Notes from Kleene, University of Wisconsin, to Montague, undated (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Comment on descriptions, Nat. Ded. Hallperin, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, Booth, McCauley, 1960 April (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Correspondence with Copi and symbolic logic, 1954 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Correspondence with I. M. Copi, 1954-1955 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Notes labelled "That", undated (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Manuscript labelled "That," Richard Montague and Donald Kalish, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- "That" paper, and correspondence with J. M. McLellan, 1958 October (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Abstract on Tarskis abstract, undated (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Predicate calculus abstracts, 1956 February (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Predicate calculus, abstracts 2-3, undated (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Abstract blanks and postcards, 1955-1956 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- "Does T's closure system imply Quines?", undated (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Qudependence of system with two rules, undated (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Tarski: Formalization of predicate logic with identity, undated (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Equivalence of two reduced systems, undated (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Removing 2,5 from the 2 rule system, undated (Box 83, Folder 20)
- Independence of system with closure, undated (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Proofs for abstract 3 and terms on completeness of identity theory, undated (Box 83, Folder 22)
- "Postulates for the Signed Integers," E. J. Lemmon, undated (Box 83, Folder 23)
- Correspondence from students and colleagues, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 24)
- Correspondence regarding project logic app., 1962-1964 (Box 83, Folder 25)
- Additional correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 26)
- Kurtzman letter, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 27)
- Correspondence regarding logic text (McGraw-Hill, Henry Holt, and Horth Holland), undated (Box 83, Folder 28)
- Prawitz's correspondence and proofs, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Natural deduction proofs: Manuscript and notes for Chapter 3 and Tarski-type substitution, undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Natural deduction proofs: Completeness of identity and desc. theory notes, undated (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Natural deduction proofs, undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Natural deduction proofs: Notes for Case 5, that of iota, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Natural deduction proofs: Completeness of identity and desc. theory, Case 6, undated (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Natural deduction proofs: Completeness of identity theory-ancient, undated (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Natural deduction proofs: Notes on axioms for classical calculus and outline, undated (Box 84, Folder 8)
- The propositional calculus (axioms sets and natural deduction), undated (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Kaplan: Demonstratives manuscript, 1977 March (Box 84, Folder 10)
- "How to Russel a Church" Frege Kripke in the Journal of Philosophy, 1975 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Gary Mar: Identity and paradoxes, undated (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Gary Mar: Metatheory of description, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Reviews of "What is the name of this Book?" Smllyan, undated (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Paradoxical inference material, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Quantum logic article from Scientific American, 1981 October (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Gary Mar's tree system and arguments, undated (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Philosophy 31: Manuscript and final exams (Summer), 1988 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Philosophy 31: Manuscript and handout, 1988 July 29 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- Philosophy 31: Manuscript and handout, 1988 July 15 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Philosophy 31: First exam and answer key (Summer), 1988 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Philosophy 31: First exam, answer key, and data sheet (Summer), 1988 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Philosophy 31: Symbolization and derivation manuscript (Summer), 1988 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 31: Handouts (Summer), 1988 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Computer printouts of derivations (Summer), 1988 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 31: Exercise 23 (Summer), 1988 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 31: Revised handouts (Summer), 1988 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 31: Handouts I and II (Summer), 1988 March 25 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 31: Second exam and answers (Summer), 1988 (Box 85, Folder 7-8)
- Philosophy 32: Records (Winter), 1992 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 32: Lecture notes (Winter), 1988 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 32: Records (Winter), 1990 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 32: Records (Winter), 1991 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 32: Records (Spring), 1990 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 31: Final exams (Summer), 1988 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Theories of descriptions (Scott, Mar, Kalish), undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
- "Soundness and Completeness of Russellian Theory of Descriptions", Gary Mar, 1979 October (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Tyler's comments and Don's replies, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 31: Course evaluations (Summer), 1988 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 31: "Symbolization Thoughts" and "Thoughts for Final" (Summer), 1988 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 134 and 32: Proof of infinite models (Summer), 1990 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 31: Lecture materials, undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Student proofs (Fall), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- David Vriend's induction problem (Fall), 1975 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Logic 33: Homework problems (Fall), 1975 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 133: Records (Fall), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 133: Materials and homework (Winter), 1972 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 133: Bibliography (Fall), 1973 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 133: Final exam questions and answers, 1974-1975 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Terms, definitions and principals for description operator and induction principle (Fall), 1975 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 133: Homework, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 133: Final examinations, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 17)
- Philosophy 133: Records and homework (Fall), 1975 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 133: Kaplan and logic, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 133: Kaplan, 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures, final exam, and additional materials (Winter), 1988 (Box 87, Folder 4-5)
- Philosophy 133: Student final examinations (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 133: Records and final examinations (Spring), 1982 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Previous handouts (Fall), 1975 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Reading Room and related book and references, 1973-1974 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 32 (Fall), 1977 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 32: Syllabus for second logic course (Spring), 1978 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 32: Lecture notes (Spring), 1978 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 32: Syllabus (Fall), 1977 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Perry Smith's text on logic, mathematics, and physics, undated (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 32: Records, exams, course evaluations (Fall), 1977 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 32: Final exam questions and answers (Winter), 1977 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 32: Student final examinations (Winter), 1977 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 32: Final exam and answer key (Spring), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 32: Tyler Burge, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 32: Lecture notes (Winter), 1973 (Box 88, Folder 9)